APPROACH  |  Spring compression 0.0 mm
GRASP  |  Spring compression 0.0 mm
CARRY  |  Spring compression 0.0 mm
ALIGN  |  Spring compression 0.0 mm
ENGAGE TERMINAL  |  Spring compression 0.0 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 0.0 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 0.4 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 2.6 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 3.4 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 4.3 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 4.9 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 5.0 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 5.6 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 5.8 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 6.0 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 6.2 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 6.1 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 6.5 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 6.8 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 6.7 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 6.9 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 6.6 mm
COMPRESS  |  Spring compression 7.0 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.0 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.1 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.2 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.3 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.4 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.5 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.7 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.9 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.8 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.7 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.6 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.5 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.4 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.3 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.2 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.1 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 7.0 mm
LOWER TILTED BATTERY  |  Spring compression 6.9 mm
RELEASE  |  Spring compression 6.9 mm
RELEASE  |  Spring compression 7.0 mm
WITHDRAW  |  Spring compression 7.0 mm
WITHDRAW  |  Spring compression 6.9 mm
POSITION EMPTY GRIPPER  |  Spring compression 7.0 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 7.0 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 7.1 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 7.2 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 7.3 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 7.4 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 7.5 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 7.7 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 7.8 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 7.9 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 8.1 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 8.2 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 8.3 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 8.4 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 8.5 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 8.6 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 8.7 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 8.8 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 8.9 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 9.0 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 9.1 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 9.2 mm
FINGERTIP PRESS  |  Spring compression 9.3 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 9.5 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 9.4 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 6.1 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 6.7 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 6.5 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 6.6 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 7.0 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 5.9 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 6.0 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 5.7 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 5.9 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 6.1 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 6.0 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 5.8 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 5.9 mm
RELEASE PRESSURE  |  Spring compression 6.0 mm
FINAL CONTACT CHECK  |  Spring compression 6.0 mm